<div>
  <p>
    pyglet is currently in alpha release, and many features are not yet fully
    documented.  If you're using pyglet today, sign up to the mailing list
    for developer support.  Let us know when you find bugs, or if you have
    a feature request.
  </p>

  <h2>mailing lists</h2>
  <p>
    The main forum for pyglet discussion is the <a
    href="http://groups.google.com/group/pyglet-users">pyglet-users</a>
    mailing list.  You can browse the mailing list online or provide your
    email address for immediate or digest updates.
  </p>

  <p>
    There are two more mailing lists if you're interested in following the
    progress of pyglet development:
  </p>

  <ul>
    <li><a
    href="http://groups.google.com/group/pyglet-issues">pyglet-issues</a> is
    an announcement list which broadcasts emails from the issue tracker.</li>

    <li><a
    href="http://groups.google.com/group/pyglet-commits">pyglet-commits</a> is
    an announcement list which broadcasts SVN commits.</li>
  </ul>

  <h2>issue tracker</h2>

  <p>The <a href="http://code.google.com/p/pyglet/issues/list">issue tracker</a>
  should be used to report any bugs or compatibility issues.</p>

  <h2>wiki</h2>

  <p>We have a <a href="wiki">wiki</a> which is primarily used for
  discussing future design aspects of pyglet.  If you'd like to contribute
  a tutorial or FAQ question though, please feel free!  Registration is
  open but requires an email address.</p>

  <h2>subversion repository</h2>

  <p>The subversion repository houses the source trunk, documentation,
  examples and development tools.  You can <a
  href="http://pyglet.googlecode.com/svn/">browse the repository</a> or check
  out a working copy using an SVN client:</p>

  <p class="console">svn checkout http://pyglet.googlecode.com/svn/trunk/
  pyglet</p>

  <h2>contact</h2>

  <p>pyglet is primarily developed by Alex Holkner.  You can reach him via
  email at <a href="Alex.Holkner@gmail.com">Alex.Holkner@gmail.com</a>.  Other
  contributors are noted in the NOTICE file of the source trunk or any source
  distribution.</p>

</div>
