<div>
  <h2>mailing lists</h2>
  <p>
    The main forum for pyglet discussion is the <a
    href="http://groups.google.com/group/pyglet-users">pyglet-users</a>
    mailing list.  You can browse the mailing list online or provide your
    email address for immediate or digest updates.
  </p>

  <p>
    There are two more mailing lists if you're interested in following the
    progress of pyglet development:
  </p>

  <ul>
    <li><a
    href="http://groups.google.com/group/pyglet-issues">pyglet-issues</a> is
    an announcement list which broadcasts emails from the issue tracker.</li>

    <li><a
    href="http://groups.google.com/group/pyglet-commits">pyglet-commits</a> is
    an announcement list which broadcasts source commits.</li>
  </ul>

  <!--
  <h2>user pages</h2>

  <p>Members of the pyglet-users mailing list can collaborate to <a
  href="http://groups.google.com/group/pyglet-users/files">upload files</a>
  and <a href="http://groups.google.com/group/pyglet-users/web">create web
  pages</a>.  Screenshots from these pages will appear on pyglet.org to
  promote your projects as well as pyglet.</p>

  <p>Members can also contribute to the <a
  href="http://groups.google.com/group/pyglet-users/web/faq">FAQ</a>, or write
  new tutorials and "howto"s.</p>
  -->

  <h2>issue tracker</h2>

  <p>The <a href="http://code.google.com/p/pyglet/issues/list">issue tracker</a>
  should be used to report any bugs or compatibility issues.  You will need
  a <a href="http://mail.google.com/mail/signup">Google account</a> to submit
  issues.</p>

  <h2>wiki</h2>

  <p>We have a <a href="http://code.google.com/p/pyglet/w/list">wiki</a> which
  is primarily used for discussing future design aspects of pyglet.  Anyone
  can read this wiki, however you must be a pyglet developer (have SVN commit
  access) to write to it.</p>

  <h2>mercurial repository</h2>

  <p>The mercurial repository houses the source trunk, documentation,
  examples and development tools.  You can <a
  href="http://code.google.com/p/pyglet/source/browse/">browse the
  repository</a> or check out a working copy using a mercurial client:</p>

  <p class="console">hg clone https://pyglet.googlecode.com/hg/ pyglet</p>

  <p>See the <a
      href="http://code.google.com/p/pyglet/source/checkout">googlecode</a>
    hosting page for more details about the repository.</p>

  <h2>contact</h2>

  <p>pyglet is developed by many individual volunteers, and there is no
    central point of contact.  If you have a question about developing with
    pyglet, or you wish to contribute a patch, please join the mailing list
    (details above).</p>

  <p>For legal issues, please contact Alex Holkner.  You can reach him via
    email at <a 
      href="mailto:Alex.Holkner@gmail.com">Alex.Holkner@gmail.com</a>.</p>

</div>
