<news>
  <item date="6-November-2007" author="Alex"
        title="pyglet 1.0 beta 1 released">
    The Beta release is now available from the <a
    href="download.html">downloads</a> page.  This release contains hundreds
    of bug fixes from the previous release, new audio drivers for Windows
    and Linux, and greater platform compatibility.
  </item>
  <item date="18-August-2007" author="Alex"
        title="pyglet 1.0 alpha 2 released">
    This alpha release fixes many bugs, includes a new audio and video
    implementation, and introduces the pyglet Programming Guide.  See the <a
    href="download.html">downloads</a> page to grab your copy.
  </item>
  <item date="9-July-2007" author="Alex"
        title="FAQ, user pages and developer wiki ready">
    The <a href="http://groups.google.com/group/pyglet-users/web/faq">FAQ</a>
    has been moved to a more permanent home where all pyglet-users members can
    contribute.  The <a
    href="http://code.google.com/p/pyglet/w/list">development wiki</a> has
    been moved to Google to make room for some forthcoming documentation.
    <p>We'd also like to point you in the direction of the <a
    href="http://groups.google.com/group/pyglet-users/web">user web
    pages</a> that can be created within the pyglet-users group.  Screenshots
    from these pages will soon be appearing on pyglet.org.</p>
  </item>
  <item date="27-June-2007" author="Alex" 
        title="pyglet 1.0 alpha released">
    This alpha release is feature complete on Linux, with only some audio and
    video issues remaining on Windows and Mac OS X.  You can start developing
    pyglet applications by downloading the SDK.
  </item>
  <item date="29-March-2007" author="Alex"
        title="Approaching Beta">
    Some major package reorganisation during the past few weeks has cleaned up
    the code base and put us on track for a Beta release in the next couple of
    months.  Work has begun on the audio and video modules, which will provide
    surround sound and support for as many codecs as you have installed.
  </item> 
</news>
